You know, in Girl Scouts, Tammie Dineesha
said you could do that with panty hose.
(Penny:)Boy, was she wrong.
Anyway, you wanna make out?
(Leonard:)I thought because our relationship's in
a beta test, you wanted to take things slow.
Okay. Do you wanna make out slow?
(Leonard:)I can go so slow it'll be like
there's a snail in your mouth.
(Leonard:)Oh...
(Penny:)Lucky for you
there's nothing else to do right now.
- Excuse me, Leonard.
- Since when don't you knock?
(Leonard:)It's, like, the only good thing about you.
(Sheldon:)Social niceties have been suspended.
We're in a state of emergency.
(Sheldon:)The world has descended
into darkened turmoil...
(Sheldon:)...lawlessness and savagery
are the order of the day.
- Fine, what is it?
- I'm making s'mores.
(Sheldon:)I wanted to alert you in case you smelled
caramelizing marshmallows...